const qa_data=[
	{"group": "Canada", "question_index": "0", "question_num": "1", "question": "What is Canada’s capital city?", "answer": "It is Ottawa.", "note":""}, 
	{"group": "Canada", "question_index": "1", "question_num": "2", "question": "Where is Canada located?", "answer": "It is above the USA.", "note":""},
	{"group": "Canada", "question_index": "2", "question_num": "2 Bonus", "question": "How many provinces does Canada have?", "answer": "It has 10 provinces.", "note":"Bonus Question"},
	{"group": "Canada", "question_index": "3", "question_num": "3", "question": "What do people in Canada eat?", "answer": "They eat poutine and pancakes with maple syrup.", "note":""},
	{"group": "Canada", "question_index": "4", "question_num": "4", "question": "What are two cities in Canada?", "answer": "They are Vancouver and Toronto.", "note":""},
	{"group": "Canada", "question_index": "5", "question_num": "4 Bonus", "question": "Which city is in the west and the east?", "answer": "Vancouver is a city in the west. Toronto is a city in the east.", "note":"Bonus Question"},
	{"group": "Canada", "question_index": "6", "question_num": "5", "question": "What is one of Canada’s holidays?", "answer": "It is New Year’s Day.", "note":""},
	{"group": "Canada", "question_index": "7", "question_num": "6", "question": "When is that holiday?", "answer": "It is on January 1st.", "note":""},
	{"group": "Canada", "question_index": "8", "question_num": "7", "question": "Who is Canada home to?", "answer": "It is home to people from many different countries.", "note":""},
	{"group": "Canada", "question_index": "9", "question_num": "8", "question": "Which season does Canada have?", "answer": "It is the fall season.", "note":""},
	{"group": "Canada", "question_index": "10", "question_num": "9", "question": "What can Canada have a lot of sometimes?", "answer": "It can sometimes have lots of snow.", "note":""},
	{"group": "India", "question_index": "0", "question_num": "1", "question": "Where is India?", "answer": "It is by Pakistan, Bangladesh and Sri Lanka.", "note":""},
	{"group": "India", "question_index": "1", "question_num": "2", "question": "What is India’s capital city?", "answer": "It is New Delhi.", "note":""},
	{"group": "India", "question_index": "2", "question_num": "3", "question": "Where is the Taj Mahal?", "answer": "It is in the city of Mumbai.", "note":""},
	{"group": "India", "question_index": "3", "question_num": "4", "question": "How many people does India have?", "answer": "They have 1.4 billion people.", "note":""},
	{"group": "India", "question_index": "4", "question_num": "5", "question": "What food do people in India eat?", "answer": "They eat curry and samosas.", "note":""},
	{"group": "India", "question_index": "5", "question_num": "6", "question": "Do they eat cows?", "answer": "No, they don’t. They love them.", "note":""},
	{"group": "India", "question_index": "6", "question_num": "7", "question": "What is a holiday in India?", "answer": "It is Holi Day.", "note":""},
	{"group": "India", "question_index": "7", "question_num": "8", "question": "When is Holi Day?", "answer": "It is on the 8th of March.", "note":""},
	{"group": "India", "question_index": "8", "question_num": "9", "question": "What is Holi Day?", "answer": "It is a festival of colors.", "note":""},
	{"group": "India", "question_index": "9", "question_num": "10", "question": "What kind of clothes do they have?", "answer": "They have colorful clothes.", "note":""},
	{"group": "Brazil", "question_index": "0", "question_num": "1", "question": "Where is Brazil?", "answer": "It is by Peru, Argentina and Bolivia.", "note":""},
	{"group": "Brazil", "question_index": "1", "question_num": "2", "question": "What is Brazil’s capital city?", "answer": "It's Brasilia.", "note":""},
	{"group": "Brazil", "question_index": "2", "question_num": "3", "question": "What is another city in Brazil?", "answer": "It is Rio de janeiro.", "note":""},
	{"group": "Brazil", "question_index": "3", "question_num": "4", "question": "Is it a big city?", "answer": "Yes, it is.", "note":""},
	{"group": "Brazil", "question_index": "4", "question_num": "5", "question": "What are two things Brazil has?", "answer": "It has the Amazon Rainforest and the Amazon River.", "note":""},
	{"group": "Brazil", "question_index": "5", "question_num": "6", "question": "What food do people in Brazil eat?", "answer": "They eat Brazilian cheese balls and black bean salad.", "note":""},
	{"group": "Brazil", "question_index": "6", "question_num": "7", "question": "What do people wear during Carnival?", "answer": "They wear bright colors.", "note":""},
	{"group": "Brazil", "question_index": "7", "question_num": "8", "question": "What do people do during Carnival?", "answer": "They dance together.", "note":""},
	{"group": "Brazil", "question_index": "8", "question_num": "9", "question": "How many times has Brazil’s football team won the World Cup?", "answer": "They have won it 5 times.", "note":""},
	{"group": "Brazil", "question_index": "9", "question_num": "10", "question": "What kind of clothes do people wear?", "answer": "They wear bright colored clothes.", "note":""},
	{"group": "France", "question_index": "0", "question_num": "1", "question": "Where is France?", "answer": "It’s by Germany, Italy and Spain.", "note":""},
	{"group": "France", "question_index": "1", "question_num": "2", "question": "What is France’s capital city?", "answer": "It is Paris.", "note":""},
	{"group": "France", "question_index": "2", "question_num": "3", "question": "What is another city in France?", "answer": "It is Lyon.", "note":""},
	{"group": "France", "question_index": "3", "question_num": "4", "question": "Where is Lyon?", "answer": "Lyon is in the south of France.", "note":""},
	{"group": "France", "question_index": "4", "question_num": "5", "question": "What do people in France like to wear?", "answer": "They like to wear fancy clothes.", "note":""},
	{"group": "France", "question_index": "5", "question_num": "6", "question": "What food do people in France eat?", "answer": "They eat croissants and Macaroons.", "note":""},
	{"group": "France", "question_index": "6", "question_num": "7", "question": "What is a holiday in France?", "answer": "It is New Year’s Day.", "note":""},
	{"group": "France", "question_index": "7", "question_num": "8", "question": "When is New Year’s Day?", "answer": "It is on January 1st.", "note":""},
	{"group": "France", "question_index": "8", "question_num": "9", "question": "What language do people speak in France?", "answer": "They speak French.", "note":""},
	{"group": "France", "question_index": "9", "question_num": "9 Bonus", "question": "What does ’hello’ mean in French?", "answer": "’Hello’ means bonjour.", "note":""},
	{"group": "France", "question_index": "10", "question_num": "10", "question": "Where do some people go on holiday in France?", "answer": "Many people like to go on holiday to Cannes.", "note":""}
];

const uniqueGroups = getUniqueGroups(qa_data);
console.log(uniqueGroups); // Output: ["Canada", "India"]


function getUniqueGroups(qa_data) {
	const uniqueGroups = new Set();
	qa_data.forEach((item) => {
    	uniqueGroups.add(item.group);
  	});
  return Array.from(uniqueGroups);
}